(Leonard:)Oh, damn it. Can I have a napkin?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, no.
But you have a whole bunch of them.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I've moved
to a four-napkin system.
(Sheldon:)Lap, hands, face
and personal emergency.
(Sheldon:)If you like, starting tomorrow
I'll add a guest napkin...
(Sheldon:)...but I'm afraid
there's nothing I can do for you today.
(Sheldon:)Good luck. That's the face napkin.
(Howard:)-So have you talked to Penny yet?
-No, I haven't.
(Howard:)-Why not?
-Because I've been busy.
(Leonard:)Because I haven't figured out a way
to bring it up.
(Leonard:)And mostly,
and I can't stress how key this is...
(Leonard:)...because I don't want to.
(Howard:)A pact is a pact.
You have to get Penny to fix me up.
(Leonard:)It's not that simple.
What am I supposed to say?
"Penny, you have any friends
you'd like to never hear from again?"
Come on. I'm smart, I have a good job.
And I have only 3 percent body fat.